export const QuizData = [
    {
        id: 1,
        leftBannerText: "Strategic Business Planning",
        heading: "Statement of readiness",
        question: "We have written 2-3 strategic plan with clear objectives and financial targets. We have a Business Plan for this year execution & reviews are a part of our life",
        optionOne: "Yes, we do have Business plans & work as per the objectives",
        optionTwo: "We work with a rough Business Plan",
        optionThree: "We don’t have any clear plans but work on our ideas",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        answerSelectedByUser: ""
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        leftBannerText: "Customers and Channels/dealers",
        heading: "Statement of readiness",
        question: "We have a deep understanding of our customer needs and they are happy with us We have a loyal channel / dealer base and work closely with them for growth",
        optionOne: "We are good at it",
        optionTwo: "We can do better",
        optionThree: "It’s a challenge",
        correctAnswer: 2,
        answerSelectedByUser: ""
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        leftBannerText: "Marketing & Demand generations effectiveness [Leads]",
        heading: "Statement of readiness",
        question: "We execute impactful ROI based lead generation plans & use Social media marketing effectively",
        optionOne: "All the time",
        optionTwo: "Sometimes - we need to focus more ",
        optionThree: "Rarely -we havent started yet",
        correctAnswer: 3,
        answerSelectedByUser: ""
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        leftBannerText: "Business Systems & Processes",
        heading: "Statement of readiness",
        question: "We have strong systems and processes across all verticals and use them effectively ",
        optionOne: "We are good at it",
        optionTwo: "Usage & adherance is a problem",
        optionThree: "We don’t have strong systems & process",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        answerSelectedByUser: ""
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        leftBannerText: "Organization",
        heading: "Statement of readiness",
        question: "We have a robust organization structure Our teams are aligned to the company goals and work together towards achieving them",
        optionOne: "Our organization is future ready",
        optionTwo: "We are working on building a strong organization",
        optionThree: "We are struggling with our organization",
        correctAnswer: 2,
        answerSelectedByUser: ""
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        leftBannerText: "Financial Performance",
        heading: "Statement of readiness",
        question: "We are meeting financial projections and budgets constantly We understand & track Profitability - we know our Gross margins, we know our costs , we know our cash flows",
        optionOne: "We are focused on it and we review it periodically ",
        optionTwo: "We plan but execution & tracking is a challenge",
        optionThree: "We find it difficult  to plan & execute Financial metrics",
        correctAnswer: 3,
        answerSelectedByUser: ""
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        leftBannerText: "Sales Management",
        heading: "Statement of readiness",
        question: "We have a strong Sales Management System, our Sales teams are skilled and competent ",
        optionOne: "We are in control ",
        optionTwo: "We have fairly good at it ",
        optionThree: "We have to work on it ",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        answerSelectedByUser: ""
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        leftBannerText: "Operations Management ",
        heading: "Statement of readiness",
        question: "Our Operations [ Manufacturing, Sales Operations, Support team, Finance and HR, Supply chain ] are robust and process driven",
        optionOne: "We are in control",
        optionTwo: "We have fairly good at it",
        optionThree: "We have to work on it",
        correctAnswer: 2,
        answerSelectedByUser: ""
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        leftBannerText: "Innovation",
        heading: "Statement of readiness",
        question: "We are innovative in our ways of working ",
        optionOne: "We are good at it ",
        optionTwo: "We can do better ",
        optionThree: "It’s a challenge ",
        correctAnswer: 3,
        answerSelectedByUser: ""
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        leftBannerText: "The CEO / Business Leader Future Readiness Outlook",
        heading: "Statement of readiness",
        question: "I am confident of the future of my business ",
        optionOne: "Yes, I am confident of my business success",
        optionTwo: "I am a little confident but need to do more for full readiness",
        optionThree: "I am not ready yet to meet the future challenges ",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        answerSelectedByUser: ""
    },
]

//export default quizData;